2go.com.ph 2013-04-30

# 2GO Group, Inc. » Privacy Policy

http://www.2GO.com.ph

**2GO** is committed to protect your personal and data privacy ("Data"). To ensure your confidence in supplying personal data related to your identification when using our website, we provide this Privacy Policy outlining our online information practices concerning how data is collected and used.

This Privacy Policy explains the types of information we gather and what we do with it. By using our website, you agree to the terms and policies described in this Privacy Policy.

Information Collected on the Site

**2GO** does not request or require any information from anonymous visitors to the website. We collect information only from those users who wish to conduct business transactions (i.e. buy or sell products or services) on the website and who have registered on our website ("Registered Users"). We limit the collection and use of data to the specific information we need to administer our business and offer you opportunities which may be of interest to you.

We require certain information (such as name, company name, city, country, e-mail address and telephone number) from Registered Users.

**2GO** will deactivate accounts of registered users that have been inactive for 18 months. Registered Users may access and change their information at any time through the website.

Use of Cookies and Log Files

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of information about the user that a website can send to your web browser which may then store it on your computer system. With the use of cookies, we can better serve you when you return to our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in future.

**Log Files**  
We may collect information regarding your IP address, browser type, domain name and access time. This information is used for our own research purposes and is separate from the Data.

Security

To maintain the accuracy of, as well as preventing from unauthorized access and ensuring the correct use of the Data, we have carried out appropriate physical, electronic and managerial measures to safeguard and secure the Data we collect online.

To better protect the Data, certain areas of the website are inaccessible unless you supply individually identifiable and verifiable information, such as your User ID / Membership Number and Password / PIN.

We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol – an industry standard for encryption over the Internet, to protect the Data. When you type in sensitive information such as credit card details, it will be automatically converted into codes before being securely dispatched over the Internet.

Provision of Information to Others

**2GO** does not provide information supplied by users to any third parties, except where law or other governmental authority otherwise requires.

Links to Other Sites

Our website may contain links to Web sites other than our own and for which we are not responsible. These websites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect information and use it in a way inconsistent with our Privacy Policy. Unless **2GO** explicitly states otherwise, such references in no way indicate our endorsement, recommendation or preference of any such products, services or information contained on any other site.

Additional Information

**2GO** may alter, update or otherwise change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. Your continued use of the website following the posting of such changes will indicate your full acceptance of those changes.

Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose the Data when required by law or court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities, or in the good faith that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including and without limitation to protect the rights or properties of **2GO**. This also applies when we have reason to believe that disclosing the Data is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.

Contact Us

For questions about our Privacy Policy, please send an email to

**webmaster@2go.com.ph**.
